Which Ninja Creamy should you get? Let's
break it down. As someone who's made
over 500 pints in the Creamy and
developed over a 100 recipes, here's
what actually matters. And stay till the
end to see this full sideby-side
comparison chart so you can screenshot
it. All right, starting off with the
original. I had mine for over 2 years.
It's absolutely amazing. Let you make so
many amazing recipes. High protein,
regular ice cream, doesn't matter. It's
got seven basic functions. It's the most
affordable at about $200, but it's loud
and often needs multiple respins. Then
there's the Ninja Creamy Deluxe. This
has bigger tubs. They're 24 ounces as
opposed to 16 ounces or a regular pint.
It also has 11 functions instead of the
normal 7. It has special things like
Italian ice, creamy chino, frozen drink.
If you want those or you're looking for
bigger portions, maybe go with this one.
But it is $250 as opposed to $200. And
then we have the Ninja Swirl, which is
what I currently have, and it is the one
that is actually a real upgrade. It's
about 50% quieter. It has more
processing power and a sharper blade, so
you don't need to respin as often. And
then obviously, you have the option to
make soft serve, but you can still make
hard ice cream just like the original
creamy. It even has a mode exclusively
for protein ice cream, which is usually
what I make, but even so, I barely use
that setting. I prefer the light ice
cream setting, so I wouldn't even factor
that in. But there are also some massive
cons. It's freaking huge, weighs like 21
lbs, and takes up a lot of counter
space. It also uses brand new pints, so
if you bought pints for your original
creamy, you can't use them. You have to
buy new ones, which is super annoying.
And most importantly, it is almost
double the price of the original creamy,
sitting at $350.
So overall, my recommendation is that if
you're buying new, I would say go for
the swirl. It's totally worth it. But if
you already have the original, don't
feel like you need to upgrade. It's not
a huge jump unless you love soft serve.
And in terms of the deluxe, I don't even
know why you'd buy that. Really only
makes sense if you want the frozen
drinks, creamy chinos, or you want a 24
ouncez pint. So yeah, here is that full
sideby-side comparison. Take a
screenshot. Feel free to share this with
anybody you know that wants to buy a
creamy. And follow me for high protein,
lowc calorie creamy recipes. I'm posting
new ones almost every single